Guide to the Secretary's Office, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Subject file, 1899-1953; Series IV
  - Vocational Guidance, Personnel Analysis, Mental and Nervous Diseases
    - Northwestern University, 1923 (Box 352, Folder 831)
    - Oberlin College, 1923 (Box 352, Folder 832)
    - Pittsburgh University, 1923-1924 (Box 352, Folder 832)
    - Princeton University, 1923 (Box 352, Folder 832)
    - Smith College, 1923 (Box 352, Folder 833)
    - Syracuse University, 1923 (Box 352, Folder 833)
    - Vassar College, 1923 (Box 352, Folder 834)
    - U.S. Department of the Interior, 1923 (Box 352, Folder 835)
    - Washington University, 1923 (Box 352, Folder 835)
    - Wisconsin State Board of Vocational Education, 1923 (Box 352, Folder 836)
    - Wyoming University, 1923 (Box 352, Folder 836)
    - Yale University, undated (Box 352, Folder 836)
    - Drafts of reports (Box 353, Folder 837)
    - Reports (Box 353, Folder 838)
    - National Research Council vocational conference, 1924 (Box 353, Folder 839)
    - Research materials (Box 353, Folder 840)
    - Printed material (Box 353, Folder 841-842)
  - Yale Pageant
    - Art School celebration, 1915 (Box 354, Folder 843)
    - Minutes of the general committee, 1915-1916 (Box 354, Folder 844)
    - Executive committee, lists and correspondence, 1915-1916 June (Box 354, Folder 845)
    - Correspondence, 1915-1916 June
      - A-B (Box 354, Folder 846)
      - C (Box 354, Folder 847)
      - D-F (Box 354, Folder 848)
      - G-J (Box 354, Folder 849)
      - K-L (Box 354, Folder 850)
      - M (Box 354, Folder 851)
      - N-Q (Box 354, Folder 852)
      - R (Box 354, Folder 853)
      - S (Box 354, Folder 854)
      - T-V (Box 354, Folder 855)
      - W-Z (Box 354, Folder 856)
    - Correspondence re: autograph pageant book, 1916 (Box 354, Folder 857)
    - Correspondence re: hotel circular, 1916 (Box 354, Folder 858)
    - Correspondence, 1916 July-October (Box 354, Folder 859)
    - Committee matter, 1916 July-October (Box 354, Folder 860)
    - Form letters and accounts, 1916 (Box 355, Folder 861)
    - Correspondence, 1916 July-October
      - A-B (Box 355, Folder 862)
      - C (Box 355, Folder 863)
      - D-G (Box 355, Folder 864)
      - H-J (Box 355, Folder 865)
      - K-L (Box 355, Folder 866)
      - M (Box 355, Folder 867)
      - N-Q (Box 355, Folder 868)
      - re: poster (Box 355, Folder 869)
      - R-S (Box 355, Folder 870)
      - T-Y (Box 355, Folder 871)
      - W-Z (Box 355, Folder 872)
    - Correspondence 1916 Oct-1917
      - A-B (Box 355, Folder 873)
      - C (Box 355, Folder 874)
      - D-G (Box 355, Folder 875)
      - H-J (Box 355, Folder 876)
      - K-M (Box 355, Folder 877)
      - N-Q (Box 355, Folder 878)
      - R-S (Box 355, Folder 879)
      - T-V (Box 355, Folder 880)
      - W-Z (Box 355, Folder 881)
    - Colleges in pageant, 1916 (Box 356, Folder 882)
    - Correspondence, 1917 (Box 356, Folder 883)
    - Printed material, 1916 (Box 356, Folder 884)